Correspondence from the Elizabeth Sprague Coolidge Foundation Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Correspondence, 1894-1953 (Box 1-109)
  - Beethoven (regarding a study in manuscripts) see D'Amato, Guy A.
  - Beethoven Association (New York, N.Y.) (Box-folder 6/14)
  - Beethoven Centennial see Sard, Frederick N.
  - Behrends, Lydia Hoffman (Box-folder 6/15)
  - Behrens, Henry (Box-folder 6/16)
  - Behymer, L.E., 1928-1929 (Box-folder 6/17)
  - Behymer, L.E., 1930 (Box-folder 6/18)
  - Behymer, L.E., 1931 (Box-folder 6/19)
  - Behymer, L.E., 1932-1941, undated (Box-folder 6/20)
  - Beigel, Victor (Box-folder 6/21)
  - "Bel" miscellaneous see also "B" miscellaneous (Box-folder 6/22)
  - Belgium (Box-folder 6/23)
  - Belgium. Ambassador (Box-folder 6/24)
  - Bell, Louise de Hauteville (Box-folder 6/25)
  - Belmont, Eleanor Robson (Mrs. August) (Box-folder 6/26)
  - Bender, Albert (Box-folder 6/27)
  - Benditzky, Naoum (Box-folder 6/28)
  - Benecke, P.V.M. (Box-folder 6/29)
  - Benigin, Bianca (Box-folder 6/30)
  - Bennett, Arnold (Box-folder 6/31)
  - Bennett, Edith (Box-folder 6/32)
  - Bennett, John Hudson (Box-folder 6/33)
  - Bennington College (Box-folder 6/34)
  - Bentley, Cyrus, Mrs. (Box-folder 6/35)
  - "Ber" miscellaneous see also "B" miscellaneous (Box-folder 6/36)
  - Berenguer Concert Management (Box-folder 6/37)
  - Berens, Cécile M. (Box-folder 6/38)
  - Berezowski, Nicolai, 1927-1934 (Box-folder 6/39)
  - Berezowski, Nicolai, 1935-1951 (Box-folder 6/40)
  - Berezowski, Nicolai, undated (Box-folder 6/41)
  - Berger, Lillian (Box-folder 6/42)
  - Bergsma, William (letter to only) (Box-folder 6/43)
  - "Berk" miscellaneous see also "B" miscellaneous (Box-folder 7/1)
  - Berkeley, Lennox (Box-folder 7/2)
  - Berkeley (University of California) see California. University. Berkeley
  - Berkshire Athenaeum (Box-folder 7/3)
  - Berkshire Evening Eagle see also Pittsfield, Massachusetts. Berkshire Evening Eagle (Box-folder 7/6)
  - Berkshire Industrial Farm (Box-folder 7/8)
  - Berkshire Life Insurance Company (Box-folder 7/9)
  - Berkshire Museum, 1934-1949 (Box-folder 7/4)
  - Berkshire Museum, 1950-1953 (Box-folder 7/5)
  - Berkshire Music Center (Box-folder 7/10)
  - Berkshire Music Colony see Library of Congress. Legal advice to E.S. Coolidge
  - Berkshire Music Festival, 1938, Thank you’s for booklet. (Box-folder 7/7)
  - Berkshire String Quartet (Box-folder 7/11)
  - Berkshire Symphonic Festival (Box-folder 7/12)
  - Berkshire (Miscellany) (Box-folder 7/13)
  - Berlin (Box-folder 7/14)
  - Bernstein, Leonard (Box-folder 7/15)
  - Bertrand, Paul (Box-folder 7/16)
  - Bessemans, A. (Box-folder 7/17)
  - Betti, Adolfo, 1921-1929 (Box-folder 7/18)
  - Betti, Adolfo, 1930-1934 (Box-folder 7/19)
  - Betti, Adolfo, 1935-1939 (Box-folder 7/20)
  - Betti, Adolfo, 1940-1941 (Box-folder 7/21)
  - Betti, Adolfo, undated (Box-folder 7/22)
  - Bettingen, Balthasar (Box-folder 7/23)
  - "Bi" miscellaneous see also "B" miscellaneous (Box-folder 8/1)
  - Bichl, Lois (Box-folder 8/2)
  - Bierhoff, Dr. Frederick and Mrs. (Box-folder 8/3)
  - Biggs, E. Power, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 8/4)
  - Biggs, E. Power, 1943 (Box-folder 8/5)
  - Biggs, E. Power, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 8/6)
  - Biggs, E. Power, 1946-1949 (Box-folder 8/7)
  - Biggs, E. Power, 1950-1951 (Box-folder 8/8)
  - Birchard, C.C. & Co. (Box-folder 8/9)
  - Bird, Remsen see Occidental College
  - Birmingham, Alabama (Box-folder 8/10)
  - Bispham, David (Box-folder 8/11)
  - Bissell, Lillian (Box-folder 8/12)
  - Bitter, Francis and Alice (Box-folder 8/13)
  - "Bl" miscellaneous see also "B" miscellaneous (Box-folder 9/1)
  - Black, Katherine Isabel (Box-folder 9/2)
  - Black Mountain College (Black Mountain, N.C.) (Box-folder 9/3)
  - Blackstone, Milton see Hart House String Quartet
  - Blackwell, Ethel M. (Box-folder 9/4)
  - Blank, Dorothy Galloway (Box-folder 9/5)
  - Blank, Harry (Box-folder 9/6)
  - Bliss, Arthur and Trudy, 1923-1929 (Box-folder 9/7)
  - Bliss, Arthur and Trudy, 1930-1941 (Box-folder 9/8)
  - Bliss, Arthur and Trudy, undated (Box-folder 9/9)
  - Bliss, Howard (Box-folder 9/10)
  - Bliss, Robert Woods and Mrs. see also Harvard University. Board of Overseers (Box-folder 9/11)
  - Bloch, Alexander (Box-folder 9/12)
  - Bloch, Ernest, 1917-1919 (Box-folder 9/13)
  - Bloch, Ernest, 1920-1929 (Box-folder 9/14)
  - Bloch, Ernest, 1930-1938, undated (Box-folder 9/15)
  - Bloch, Ivan (Box-folder 9/16)
  - Blodgett, Margaret (Box-folder 9/17)
  - Blomberg, A.M. von (Box-folder 9/21)
  - Blonay, André de (Box-folder 9/18)
  - Blondel, R. (Box-folder 9/19)
  - Bloom, Frances (Box-folder 9/20)
  - Bloomfield-Zeisler, Fannie see Zeisler, Fannie Bloomfield
  - Blumberg, Lulu J. see Wind Instrument Ensemble of San Francisco
  - Blumenstehl, Paul (Box-folder 9/22)
  - "Bo" miscellaneous see also "B" miscellaneous (Box-folder 9/23)
  - Bodanzky, Artur (Box-folder 9/24)
  - Bodge, Wilma Mayberry (Box-folder 9/25)
  - Bodky, Erwin (Box-folder 9/26)
  - Boepple, Paul (Box-folder 9/27)
  - Boetzelaer, W. de, Baron (Box-folder 9/28)
  - Bogue-Laberge Concert Management (Box-folder 9/29)
  - Bohemian Club (Box-folder 9/30)
  - Bohet, Victor (Box-folder 9/31)
  - Bohlen, Frank and Ingrid (Box-folder 9/32)
  - Bok, Mary Louise Curtis (Box-folder 9/33)
  - Bolm, Adolph (Box-folder 9/34)
  - Bonis, Mél see Domange, Albert, Mrs.
  - Bonnet, Joseph (Box-folder 9/35)
  - Bonsal, Stephan (Box-folder 9/36)
  - Bonucci, Arturo (Box-folder 9/37)
  - Bonvalot, Cecil (Box-folder 9/38)
  - Boosey & Hawkes (Box-folder 9/39)
  - Bori, Lucrezia (Box-folder 9/40)
  - Borissoff, Josef (Box-folder 9/41)
  - Borowski, Felix (Box-folder 9/42)
  - Bos, Coenraad Valentyn (Box-folder 9/43)
  - Boshco, Peter and Mrs. (Box-folder 9/44)
  - Bossan, Lola (Box-folder 9/45)
  - Bossi, Adolfo (Box-folder 9/46)
  - Bossi, Renzo (Box-folder 9/47)
  - Boston Chamber Music Club (Box-folder 10/1)
  - Boston Chamber Music Guild (Box-folder 10/2)
  - Boston Chamber Recording Artists (Box-folder 10/3)
  - Boston, Mass. Chilton Club (Box-folder 10/4)
  - Boston. Chorus Pro Musica (Box-folder 10/5)
  - Boston, City of (Box-folder 10/6)
  - Boston Conservatory (Box-folder 10/7)
  - Boston, Mass. Ford Hall Forum (Box-folder 10/8)
  - Boston. Hotel Statler (Box-folder 10/9)
  - Boston Museum of Fine Arts (Box-folder 10/10)
  - Boston Musical Association see also Longy, Georges (Box-folder 10/11)
  - Boston Negro American Chorus see Simms, Ernest W.
  - Boston Public Library, 1925-1929 (Box-folder 10/12)
  - Boston Public Library, 1930-1953 (Box-folder 10/13)
  - Boston Society of Early Music (Box-folder 10/14)
  - Boston Symphony Orchestra, 1923-1938 (Box-folder 10/15)
  - Boston Symphony Orchestra, 1939-1942 (Box-folder 10/16)
  - Boston Symphony Orchestra, 1943-1949 (Box-folder 10/17)
  - Boston Symphony Orchestra, 1950-1951 (Box-folder 10/18)
  - Boston Symphony Orchestra, 1952-1953, undated (Box-folder 10/19)
  - Boston University (Box-folder 10/20)
  - Boston. Women's Music Association (Box-folder 10/21)
  - Boston. Hotels (Box-folder 10/22)
  - Boston. Newspapers (Box-folder 10/23)
  - Boston. Miscellany (Box-folder 10/24)
  - "Bostona" miscellaneous (Box-folder 10/25)
  - Bote & Bock (Box-folder 10/26)
  - Boulanger, Nadia (Box-folder 10/27)
  - Boult, Adrian (Box-folder 10/28)
  - Bourdon, Louis H. (Box-folder 10/29)
  - Bourke-White, Margaret (Box-folder 10/30)
  - Bowen, Catherine Drinker (Box-folder 10/31)
  - Bowen, Edith Blumer (Box-folder 10/32)
  - Bowen, York (Box-folder 10/33)
  - Bowerman, George F. see District of Columbia. Public Library
  - Boy Scouts of America, Elizabeth Sprague Coolidge Troop see also Cagayan Valley College (Box-folder 11/1)
  - Boyd, Ellen Edwards (Box-folder 11/2)
  - Boyes, Shibley (Box-folder 11/3)
  - Boys' Clubs see also Millikan, Robert A. (Box-folder 11/4)
  - "Bra" miscellaneous see also "B" miscellaneous (Box-folder 11/5)
  - Brady, Margaret Greer (Box-folder 11/6)
  - Brambilla, Ormida (Box-folder 11/7)
  - Brandeis, Louis (Box-folder 11/8)
  - Brandeis University (Box-folder 11/9)
  - Brandt, Stella S. (Box-folder 11/10)
  - Branscombe, Gena (Box-folder 11/11)
  - Braslau, Sophie (Box-folder 11/12)
  - Brattleboro Music School (Box-folder 11/13)
  - Brauer, Olga (Box-folder 11/14)
  - Braun, Ida S. (Box-folder 11/15)
  - Brazier, Emma Jeannette (Box-folder 11/16)
  - "Bre" miscellaneous see also "B" miscellaneous (Box-folder 11/17)
  - Breed, William C., Mrs. see New York Philharmonic Symphony Orchestra
  - Brennan, F. E., Mrs. (Box-folder 11/19)
  - Brentano's (Box-folder 11/18)
  - Brescia, Cinina see Warren, Cinina Brescia
  - Brescia, Domenico, 1921-1929 (Box-folder 11/20)
  - Brescia, Domenico, 1930-1933 (Box-folder 11/21)
  - Brescia, Domenico, 1934-1940 (Box-folder 11/22)
  - Brescia, Domenico, undated (Box-folder 11/23)
  - "Bri" miscellaneous see also "B" miscellaneous (Box-folder 11/24)
  - Bricken, Carl see also Wisconsin. University and Chicago. University (Box-folder 11/25)
  - Brickenstein, Mary and Lucy (Box-folder 11/26)
  - Brico, Antonia (managerial) (Box-folder 11/27)
  - Bridge, Frank and Ethel, 1922 (Box-folder 12/1)
  - Bridge, Frank and Ethel, 1923 (Box-folder 12/2)
  - Bridge, Frank and Ethel, 1924 (Box-folder 12/3)
  - Bridge, Frank and Ethel, undated, Material from 1922-1924 folders. (Box-folder 12/4)
  - Bridge, Frank and Ethel, 1925 (Box-folder 12/5)
  - Bridge, Frank and Ethel, 1926 (Box-folder 12/6)
  - Bridge, Frank and Ethel, 1927 (Box-folder 12/7)
  - Bridge, Frank and Ethel, 1928 (Box-folder 12/8)
  - Bridge, Frank, 1929 (Box-folder 12/9)
  - Bridge, Frank, 1930 (Box-folder 12/10)
  - Bridge, Frank, 1931 (Box-folder 12/11)
  - Bridge, Frank, 1932 (Box-folder 12/12)
  - Bridge, Frank, undated, Material from 1928-1932 folders. (Box-folder 12/13)
  - Bridge, Frank, 1933 (Box-folder 12/14)
  - Bridge, Frank, 1934 (Box-folder 12/15)
  - Bridge, Frank, 1935 (Box-folder 12/16)
  - Bridge, Frank, 1936 (Box-folder 12/17)
  - Bridge, Frank, 1937 (Box-folder 12/18)
  - Bridge, Frank, 1938 (Box-folder 12/19)
  - Bridge, Frank, 1939 (Box-folder 12/20)
  - Bridge, Frank, 1940 (Box-folder 12/21)
  - Bridge, Ethel, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 12/22)
  - Bridge, Ethel, 1943-1945 (Box-folder 12/23)
  - Bridge, Ethel, 1946-1949 (Box-folder 12/24)
  - Bridge, Ethel, 1950-1953 (Box-folder 12/25)
  - Bridge, Frank and Ethel, undated (Box-folder 12/26)
  - Bridges, Robert, Mrs. (Box-folder 12/27)
  - Brightenburg, Paul (Box-folder 12/28)
  - Bristol, Mary A., 1921-1929 (Box-folder 13/1)
  - Bristol, Mary A., 1930-1933 (Box-folder 13/2)
  - Bristol, Mary A., 1934-1937 (Box-folder 13/3)
  - Bristol, Mary A., 1938 (Box-folder 13/4)
  - Bristol, Mary A., 1939-1941 (Box-folder 13/5)
  - Bristol, Mary A., 1942 (Box-folder 13/6)
  - Bristol, Mary A., undated (Box-folder 13/7)
  - Britt, Horace, 1924-1939 (Box-folder 13/8)
  - Britt, Horace, 1941-1960 (Box-folder 13/9)
  - Britt, Horace, undated (Box-folder 13/10)
  - Britt, Horace, Contains Christmas and greeting cards. (Box-folder 13/11)
  - Britten, Benjamin (Box-folder 13/12)
  - "Bro" miscellaneous see also "B" miscellaneous (Box-folder 13/13)
  - Broadcasting companies see New York. Municipal Broadcasting System
  - Brockway, Howard (Box-folder 13/14)
  - Brodetsky, Julian (Box-folder 13/15)
  - Brodsky, Herbert (Box-folder 13/16)
  - Bronson, Ilya (Box-folder 13/17)
  - Brookings, Isabel (Box-folder 13/18)
  - Brooks, Ernest (Box-folder 13/19)
  - "Bros" miscellaneous see also "B" miscellaneous (Box-folder 14/1)
  - Brosa, Antonio and Peggy, 1929-1935 (Box-folder 14/2)
  - Brosa, Antonio and Peggy, 1937-1942 (Box-folder 14/3)
  - Brosa, Antonio and Peggy, 1943-1949 (Box-folder 14/4)
  - Brosa, Antonio and Peggy, 1950-1953 (Box-folder 14/5)
  - Brosa, Antonio and Peggy, undated (Box-folder 14/6)
  - Brower, Harriette (Box-folder 14/8)
  - Brown, Annie Florence see The Oakland Forum
  - Brown, Arthur, Jr. see San Francisco Art Association
  - Brown, Caroline Arthur (Box-folder 14/9)
  - Brown, Eddy (Box-folder 14/10)
  - Brown, Elizabeth Sutton (Box-folder 14/11)
  - Brown, John Nicholas (Box-folder 14/12)
  - Brown University (Box-folder 14/13)
  - Brown, Wilson see United States Naval Academy
  - Browne & Nichols School, Cambridge, Massachusetts (Box-folder 14/7)
  - Brownrigg, Ethel Parks (Box-folder 14/14)
  - "Bru" miscellaneous see also "B" miscellaneous (Box-folder 14/15)
  - Bruckner Society of America (Box-folder 14/16)
  - Bruneau, Alfred (Box-folder 14/17)
  - Brunswick, Mark (Box-folder 14/18)
  - Brussel, Robert (Box-folder 14/19)
  - Brussels. Conservatoire royal de musique (Box-folder 14/20)
  - Brussels. Palais des beaux-arts (Box-folder 14/21)
  - Brussels. Société philharmonique (Box-folder 14/22)
  - Brussels. Université (Box-folder 14/23)
  - Brussels. Miscellany (Box-folder 14/24)
  - Bruyn, Gertrude V. see Mount Holyoke College
  - Bryan, Gordon (Box-folder 14/25)
  - Bryn Mawr (Box-folder 14/26)
  - "Bu" miscellaneous see also "B" miscellaneous (Box-folder 15/1)
  - Buch, Richard (Box-folder 15/2)
  - Buck, Dudley (Box-folder 15/3)
  - Buck, Pearl (Box-folder 15/4)
  - Budapest String Quartet (Box-folder 15/5)
  - Budapest-Trio (Box-folder 15/6)
  - Budapest (Box-folder 15/7)
  - Buffalo Symphony Orchestra (and other things from Buffalo, N.Y.) (Box-folder 15/8)
  - Buffin, Baron Victor (Box-folder 15/9)
  - Buhler, Ulysse (Box-folder 15/10)
  - Buhlig, Richard (Box-folder 15/11)
  - Bulfinch Street Church see Ives, Henry G.
  - Bulletin of the Atomic Scientists see also Urey, Harold C. (Box-folder 15/12)
  - Bunche, Ralph J. (material about him only) see also United Nations Fund of the American Association for the United Nations, Inc. (Box-folder 15/13)
  - Burdick, A. A., Mrs. (Box-folder 15/14)
  - Bureau of Educational Experiments (Box-folder 15/15)
  - Burg, Willem van den see Van den Burg, William
  - Burgin, Richard (Box-folder 15/16)
  - Burgsthal, Richard (Box-folder 15/17)
  - Burian, Hans (Box-folder 15/18)
  - Burlin, Natalie Curtis (Box-folder 15/19)
  - Burling, Louise (Box-folder 15/20)
  - Burr, Allston (Box-folder 15/21)
  - Burr, Johanna Hess (Box-folder 15/22)
  - Busch, Adolf (Box-folder 15/23)
  - Busch String Quartet (Box-folder 15/24)
  - Butler, Nicholas Murray see Columbia University. Nicholas Murray Butler
  - Buxbaum, Walter see Thacher School
  - Byrnes, Alice S. (Mrs. Eugene Byrnes) (Box-folder 15/25)
  - Byrns, Harold (Box-folder 15/26)
  - "B" unidentified (Box-folder 15/27)
  - "C" miscellaneous (Box-folder 16/1)
  - Cabot, Henry B. (Box-folder 16/2)
  - Cabot, Richard C. (Box-folder 16/3)
  - Čadek, Ottokar T. (Box-folder 16/4)
  - Cadman, Charles Wakefield (Box-folder 16/5)
  - Cagayan Valley College see also Boy Scouts of America, Elizabeth Sprague Coolidge Troop (Box-folder 16/6)
  - Cage, John (Box-folder 16/7)
  - Cahan, Sydney S. (Box-folder 16/8)
  - Cahier, Sara Jane (Mrs. Charles Cahier) (Box-folder 16/9)
  - Cahill, Mary D. (Box-folder 16/10)
  - Cahuzac, Louis (Box-folder 16/11)
  - Caldwell, Emily L. (Box-folder 16/12)
  - Caldwell, Gladys, 1914-1928 see also Los Angeles Public Library (Box-folder 16/13)
  - Caldwell, Gladys, 1929 (Box-folder 16/14)
  - Caldwell, Gladys, 1930 (Box-folder 16/15)
  - Caldwell, Gladys, 1931 (Box-folder 16/16)
  - Caldwell, Gladys, 1932 (Box-folder 16/17)
  - Caldwell, Gladys, 1933 (Box-folder 16/18)
  - Caldwell, Gladys, 1934 (Box-folder 16/19)
  - Caldwell, Gladys, 1935 (Box-folder 16/20)
  - Caldwell, Gladys, 1936 (Box-folder 16/21)
  - Caldwell, Gladys, 1937 (Box-folder 16/22)
  - Caldwell, Gladys, 1938 (Box-folder 16/23)
  - Caldwell, Gladys, 1939 (Box-folder 16/24)
  - Caldwell, Gladys, 1940 (Box-folder 16/25)
  - Caldwell, Gladys, 1941 (Box-folder 16/26)
  - Caldwell, Gladys, 1942 (Box-folder 16/27)
  - Caldwell, Gladys, 1943 (Box-folder 16/28)
  - Caldwell, Gladys, 1944 (Box-folder 16/29)
  - Caldwell, Gladys, 1945 (Box-folder 16/30)
  - Caldwell, Gladys, 1946 (Box-folder 16/31)
  - Caldwell, Gladys, 1947 (Box-folder 16/32)
  - Caldwell, Gladys, 1948 (Box-folder 16/33)
  - Caldwell, Gladys, 1949 (Box-folder 16/34)
  - Caldwell, Gladys, 1950 (Box-folder 16/35)
  - Caldwell, Gladys, undated (Box-folder 16/36)
  - Caldwell, Gladys (to Caldwell), undated (Box-folder 16/37)
  - "Calh" miscellaneous see also "C" miscellaneous (Box-folder 17/1)
  - Calhoun, Lucy (Box-folder 17/2)
  - California Institute of Technology (Box-folder 17/3)
  - California Society of Composers (Box-folder 17/4)
  - California. University. Berkeley. Deutsch, Monroe E. (Box-folder 17/5)
  - California. University. Berkeley. Elkus, Albert, 1933-1939 (Box-folder 17/6)
  - California. University. Berkeley. Elkus, Albert, 1940-circa 1952 (Box-folder 17/7)
  - California. University. Berkeley. Elkus, Albert, undated (Box-folder 17/8)
  - California. University. Berkeley. Popper, William (Box-folder 17/9)
  - California. University. Berkeley. Sproul, Robert Gordon and Ida, 1931-1934 (Box-folder 17/10)
  - California. University. Berkeley. Sproul, Robert Gordon and Ida, 1935-1936 (Box-folder 17/11)
  - California. University. Berkeley. Sproul, Robert Gordon and Ida, 1937-1939 (Box-folder 17/12)
  - California. University. Berkeley. Sproul, Robert Gordon and Ida, 1940-1948 (Box-folder 17/13)
  - California. University. Berkeley. Sproul, Robert Gordon and Ida, undated (Box-folder 17/14)
  - California. University. Berkeley. Miscellany (Box-folder 17/15)
  - California. University. Los Angeles (Box-folder 17/16)
  - California. University of Southern California see Southern California. University
  - California. Miscellany (Box-folder 17/17)
  - Callaway, Paul (Box-folder 17/18)
  - "Cam" miscellaneous see also "C" miscellaneous (Box-folder 18/1)
  - Cambridge, Massachusetts. City government (Box-folder 18/2)
  - Cambridge, Massachusetts. Society for Early Music (Box-folder 18/3)
  - Cambridge Trust Company (Box-folder 18/4)
  - Cambridge, Massachusetts. Miscellany (Box-folder 18/5)
  - Camley, A.M. (Box-folder 18/6)
  - Campbell, Ada Rumsey (Mrs. Treat Campbell) (Box-folder 18/7)
  - Campbell, Ivy Meldrum (Box-folder 18/8)
  - Campbell, Napoleon A. and Mrs. (Mary P. Campbell) (Box-folder 18/9)
  - Cann, F. Louis (Box-folder 18/10)
  - Cantacuzène, Julia (Box-folder 18/11)
  - Cape Cod Institute of Music (Box-folder 18/12)
  - Cappel, C.C., 1936-1941 (Box-folder 18/13)
  - Cappel, C.C., 1942 (Box-folder 18/14)
  - Cappel, C.C., 1943 (Box-folder 18/15)
  - Cappel, C.C., 1944 (Box-folder 18/16)
  - Carabo, Madeline (Box-folder 18/17)
  - Carfagno, Simon (Box-folder 18/18)
  - Carl, William C. (Box-folder 18/19)
  - Carl Fischer Inc. see Fischer, Carl (firm)
  - Carll, Lotta (Box-folder 18/20)
  - Carmosino, Mario (Box-folder 18/21)
  - Carnegie Hall (Box-folder 18/22)
  - Carolina Art Association (Box-folder 18/23)
  - Carpenter, George A. and Mrs. (Box-folder 18/24)
  - Carpenter, John Alden and Ellen, 1917-1932 (Box-folder 18/25)
  - Carpenter, John Alden and Ellen, 1933 (Box-folder 18/26)
  - Carpenter, John Alden and Ellen, 1934-1939 (Box-folder 18/27)
  - Carpenter, John Alden and Ellen, 1940-1945 (Box-folder 18/28)
  - Carpenter, John Alden and Ellen, undated (Box-folder 18/29)
  - Carpenter, Nellie, 1921-1932 (Box-folder 18/30)
  - Carpenter, Nellie, 1933-1934 (Box-folder 18/31)
  - Carpenter, Nellie, 1935-1937 (Box-folder 18/32)
  - Carpenter, Nettie (Box-folder 18/33)
  - Carr, Lillian (Mrs. Clyde Carr) (Box-folder 18/34)
  - Carreño, Teresa (Box-folder 18/35)
  - Carriére, Henri Bouvier (Box-folder 18/36)
  - Carrington, Margaret (Mrs. William T. Carrington) (Box-folder 18/37)
  - Carroll, Amy Keith (Box-folder 18/38)
  - Carruth, William W. and Mrs. (Box-folder 18/39)
  - Carson, Nellie (Box-folder 18/40)
  - Carter, Artie Mason (Box-folder 18/41)
  - Carter, Elliott Cook (Box-folder 18/42)
  - Carter, Mabel S. (Box-folder 18/43)
  - Casadesus, Henri (Box-folder 18/44)
  - Casadesus, Marius (Box-folder 18/45)
  - Casadesus, Robert (Box-folder 18/46)
  - Casals, Pablo, 1917-1929 (Box-folder 18/47)
  - Casals, Pablo, 1930-1952 (Box-folder 18/48)
  - Casals, Susan Metcalfe, 1917-1919 (Box-folder 18/49)
  - Casals, Susan Metcalfe, 1920-1927 (Box-folder 18/50)
  - Casals, Susan Metcalfe, undated (Box-folder 18/51)
  - Casals Festivals (Box-folder 18/52)
  - "Case" miscellaneous see also "C" miscellaneous (Box-folder 19/1)
  - Casella, Alfredo and Yvonne, 1922-1924 (Box-folder 19/2)
  - Casella, Alfredo and Yvonne, 1925 (Box-folder 19/3)
  - Casella, Alfredo and Yvonne, 1926-1928 (Box-folder 19/4)
  - Casella, Alfredo and Yvonne, 1929 (Box-folder 19/5)
  - Casella, Alfredo and Yvonne, 1930-1931 (Box-folder 19/6)
  - Casella, Alfredo and Yvonne, 1932-1933 (Box-folder 19/7)
  - Casella, Alfredo and Yvonne, 1934 (Box-folder 19/8)
  - Casella, Alfredo and Yvonne, 1935-1936 (Box-folder 19/9)
  - Casella, Alfredo and Yvonne, 1937-1945 (Box-folder 19/10)
  - Casella, Alfredo and Yvonne, undated (Box-folder 19/11)
  - Casella, Enrique (Box-folder 19/12)
  - Castelnuovo-Tedesco, Mario, 1929-1931 (Box-folder 19/13)
  - Castelnuovo-Tedesco, Mario, 1933-1950, undated (Box-folder 19/14)
  - Castle, Margaret F. (Mrs. William R. Castle) (Box-folder 19/15)
  - Castro, Juan José (Box-folder 19/16)
  - Cate, Marian Wolsey (Box-folder 19/17)
  - Cathedral Choral Society, Washington, D.C. (Box-folder 19/18)
  - Cave-Cole, Ethel (Box-folder 19/19)
  - CBS see Columbia Broadcasting System
  - "Ce" miscellaneous see also "C" miscellaneous (Box-folder 19/20)
  - Central Union Trust (Box-folder 19/21)
  - Century Association (Box-folder 19/22)
  - Century of Progress International Exposition (1933-1934: Chicago, Ill.) (Box-folder 19/23)
  - Ceriani, Edwige Balbi (Box-folder 19/24)
  - "Ch" miscellaneous see also "C" miscellaneous (Box-folder 19/25)
  - Chabay, Leslie (Box-folder 19/26)
  - Chadwick, George Whitefield (Box-folder 19/27)
  - Chaffee, Marie Kreutz (Box-folder 19/28)
  - Chalifoux, Alice (Box-folder 19/29)
  - Chalmers, Gordon see Kenyon College
  - Chalmers, William J. and Mrs. (Box-folder 19/30)
  - Chalupt, René (Box-folder 19/31)
  - Chamber Music Society of Kansas City, Missouri see Kansas City, Missouri: Chamber Music Society of
  - Chamber Music Society of San Francisco see San Francisco, Chamber Music Society of
  - Chamberlain, Edith (Mrs. Selah Chamberlain) (Box-folder 19/32)
  - Chambers, Bert Coe, Mrs. (Box-folder 19/33)
  - Chandler, Roy (Box-folder 19/34)
  - Chanler, Margaret (Mrs. Winthrop Chanler) (Box-folder 19/35)
  - Chapin, Rosamond (Box-folder 19/36)
  - Chapiro, Fania (Box-folder 19/37)
  - Charbonel, Avis Bliven (Box-folder 19/38)
  - Chardon, Yves (Box-folder 19/39)
  - Charleston, S.C. (Box-folder 19/40)
  - Charlton, Loudon (Box-folder 19/41)
  - Charpentier, Gustave (Box-folder 19/42)
  - Chase, Gilbert (report on the American Music Libraries Loan Project) (Box-folder 19/43)
  - Chase, William (Box-folder 19/44)
  - Chaumont, Émile (Box-folder 19/45)
  - Chávez, Carlos, 1936 (Box-folder 19/46)
  - Chávez, Carlos, 1937 (Box-folder 19/47)
  - Chávez, Carlos, 1938-1939 (Box-folder 19/48)
  - Chávez, Carlos, 1940-1962, undated (Box-folder 19/49)
  - Cheatham, Kitty (Box-folder 19/50)
  - Chennevière, Daniel see Rudhyar, Dane
  - Cherkassky, Eugenie (Box-folder 19/51)
  - Cherkassky, Paul (Box-folder 19/52)
  - Chessé, Ralph (Box-folder 19/53)
  - Chevy Chase Club (Chevy Chase, Md.) (Box-folder 19/54)
  - "Chi" miscellaneous see also "C" miscellaneous (Box-folder 20/1)
  - Chicago A Cappella Choir (Box-folder 20/2)
  - Chicago. Art Institute of Chicago (Box-folder 20/3)
  - Chicago. Arts Club (Box-folder 20/4)
  - Chicago. Civic Music Association see also Borowski, Felix (Box-folder 20/5)
  - Chicago Civic Opera Company (Box-folder 20/6)
  - Chicago. Cliff Dwellers (Box-folder 20/7)
  - Chicago. The Cordon (Box-folder 20/8)
  - Chicago. Exposition, 1933 see Chicago Civic Opera Company